

CRISTIAN PÉREZ

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFILE

4+ years of work experience in thefinancial sector using .Net and SQL technologies, I was in the support area for a fintech app (Android native)

1 year of work in entertainment habit using .Net, ansible and SQL technologies

1 year of work developing for the general technology using full stack frameworks

CONTACT



isc.cristian.perez.54@gmail.

52 (786) 102 1588

EDUCATION

2012 - 2017

TecNM Campus Ciudad Hidalgo software engineering specialty

2017 - 2018

TecNM Campus Ciudad Hidalgo Computer Systems Engineer title

LANGUAGES

Basic English (Reading, writing and listening to the language)

SKILLS

- C#(MVC, .NET, WCF, Entity Framework)
- Web Services(SOAP, REST)
- Javascript Frameworks(Angular JS, Vue JS, React JS, Node JS)
- UX/UI Technologies(Bootstrap, CSS, awesome fonts)
- Ansible
- SQL(SQL server, MySQL)
- Versioning Code(Git,Bitbucket)
- Sprits and activities administration(Jira, Trello, Asana)
- · Autodidact, proactive, passionate about technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android(Front-End) & FullStack Developer - PagaPhone

JANUARY 2022 - TODAY

- Development of new functionality with kotlin,xml and java and new Endpoints POST were consumed for cashIn, cashOut movements for the wallet Pagaphone
- Development of new functionality for the generation of a new user reference code in the wallet PagaPhone
- Development fullstack/.NET solutions for new projects and new & solution for issues in the wallet PagaPhone

IT Coordinator - .NET - Cinépolis

JUNE 2021 - JANUARY 2022

- Support and development of new functionalities with .NET(C#, Xamarin) and SQL(SQL Server, MySQL) for
- automatic lockers from Mexico cinemas(Cinépolis)
 Support and development of new functionalities with
 .NET(C#, Xamarin) and SQL(SQL Server, MySQL) for
- automatic lockers from Spain cinemas(Yelmo)
 Support and development of new functionalities with
 .NET(C#, Xamarin) and SQL(SQL Server, MySQL) for
- automatic lockers from Chile cinemas(Hoyts)
 Development of windows services and store procedures for the automatic synchronization of the food on sale in
- the cinemas(Chile, Mexico)
 Development of windows service and store procedures for the automatic synchronization of the food on sale in the delivery UberEats(Chile, Mexico)

Developer - FullStack/.NET - Caja Morelia Valladolid

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JUNE 2021

- Development of a service layer (back-end) type SOAP / Rest with .NET and SQL Server for digital banking.
- Windows service development / scheduled tasks
- Integration of applications with providers (STP, Gesto Pago, Anzen, Gemalto, Prosa)
- Implementation of store procedure SQL-Server and Mysql
- Development of Call Center platform(Web) using .NET Technology(MVC, C#, Entity Framework), SQL Server and the PRESENCE implementation for the digital banking
- Development and implementation of the users administrator system for digital banking (Windows-Form).
- Development and implementation of recovery password(Web) using .NET and SQL Server for digital banking
- Development and implementation of OpenBank using CSS, PHP and SQL Server; development of openBank Web Service REST(.NET)
- Documentation an development of Web Services using Swagger(.NET, SQL Server).
- Solution of general issues (.NET, SQL Server, Java, JavaScript, Pascal).

Developer - FullStack - N'Corto Delivery (Freelance)

FEBRUARY 2021 - JUNE 2021

- Development interface of this delivery(Angular js)
- Development of new endpoints for the delivery(Node JS, JavaScript, MySQL)
- Documentation of use Cases for the puntual user
- Solution of general issues (.NET, SQL Server, Java, JavaScript, Pascal).

Developer - Back- End-DSI(Freelance)

JULY 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Development of new endpoints for the Cabastic app(PHP, MySQL)
- Documentation of use Cases for the puntual user
- Solution of general issues (MySQL, Javascript, PHP).

Developer - FullStack - Deipi.com

FEBRUARY 2017 - JULY 2017

- Development of new catalogue projects using React-Redux Framework
- Documentation of use Cases for the puntual user
- Generation of new Views